{
    "id": "de816a35f2dc4413aabde1aef918d886",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Take",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She takes ………………… her grandmother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "off",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6538958540014ff8a8e2bba52f750df9"
        },
        {
            "question": "They assaulted the watchmen and took many precious paintings ………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "down",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b32003b9c6914cdd8331e03f33080547"
        },
        {
            "question": "These shoes don’t fit. I am going to take them ………………… .. to the store.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "back",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed4f90f3befd4c08b4a1bb58e264f60b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t take him ………………….. an idiot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5c8ae1e23844b70bc54e84869113175"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dress was loose for me so I took it to the tailor and got it taken …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4edea9bc92744d6abed005fe15bf3ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please take your shoes ………………… .. before entering the temple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "877c033a376945b49c2637127ecf20f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "How are you going to meet the deadlines if you take ………………… . too many projects?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0d5073b293748daad42c2e69b53a55f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you love Susie why don’t you take her ………………… on a date?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e800204cc4be499fa32f326b1cea9d70"
        },
        {
            "question": "He took ………………… farming after retirement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd0f3932d9584a70b12ef3a1fddf936b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will take this issue ………………… . when we meet next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b83667a418e749e19f4f2b89d7a1d3e3"
        }
    ]
}